Guide to the Oral History of the American Left Collection OH.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series X. Radio Free Maine Tapes, May 13-14, 1994
  Duration: 200 minutes in three parts
  - Radio Free Maine Tapes -- Electronic Records, cuid36303
  - Original Audio Recordings (Box 81, Audiocassette 2-4)
  - Marketing Materials (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Series XI. Remembering Emma, May 24, 1990
  - Remembering Emma -- Electronic Records, cuid36304
  - Original Video Recordings (Box Shared Tamiment 176, U-matic 002.0177-0178)